const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '638 − 366 =', answer: '272', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '732 − 281 =', answer: '451', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '643 − 271 =', answer: '372', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '706 − 493 =', answer: '213', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '917 − 285 =', answer: '632', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '753 − 341 =', answer: '412', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '674 − 273 =', answer: '401', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '832 − 361 =', answer: '471', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '846 − 265 =', answer: '581', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '975 − 293 =', answer: '682', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];